[Music]
Marie can I have that information for
mr. Rasheed's group he'll be here in a
few minutes I'm working as fast as I can
mr. Evans will be with you very soon
that's fine I'm a little early aren't I
just a few minutes is your last name
pronounced LePage it's Lapage actually
oh that's beautiful thank you now is it
MS Lapage or mrs. Lapage
it's MS but you can call me by my first
name do you mind if I call you ms Lapage
I love the way it sounds it's fine
I'm keeping you from your work aren't I
I'm sorry I'd love to talk but I really
have to get this done right away I
understand you're not from here are you
excuse me your accent you come from
France don't you yes the Paris actually
that's nice
it sure is a beautiful day isn't it can
I have that information I'm not quite
done what's taking so long
this is Beatty I can take you to mr.
Evans office he'll be here shortly why
thank you beautiful day isn't it yes it
is Paul we have our first group from
India coming next week since mr. Rashid
has traveled to India many times I've
asked him to talk to you about etiquette
in India mr. Rashid Paul why don't you
greet me as if I were an Indian tourists
asked me to come with you and show me to
the tour bus okay hi there I'm Paul if I
were an Indian woman you would have just
insulted me
women and men generally do not touch
okay hi there you just told me to go
away you should stand this far away from
someone instead of shaking hands to this
and say namaste namaste
excellent now tell me to come with you
to the tour bus okay come with me
this is a new gesture in India do it
like this come with me
good to the bus over there I know I just
insulted you pointing with your fingers
is considered impolite use your chin
instead to the bus over there I'm never
gonna get this doing wonderful thank you
mister Oh
let's get miss Novak's tickets ready she
may be stopping by this afternoon oh are
you okay no I feel awful what's wrong
I've got this horrible cold I'm sneezing
my back is killing me I've got this pain
at my hip my necks been bothering me all
day and I have a stomachache you may
have to go see a doctor no I hate
doctors I wonder what could be wrong
maybe he's allergic to work kidding here
I used to want to be a doctor you know
say ah I remember why I didn't become a
doctor Oh Paul you really must get some
medical help a little acupuncture might
help you feel better
mr. Evans downstairs in the cafe should
we ask her to come up she may be able to
help great idea I'll go get her you
might prefer an herbal remedy I got the
cold last night
and the pain of my back started this
morning want to try a little spiritual
healing laughter is the best medicine
you know
[Music]
say ah
cover your face doc well you have a cold
that's for sure what about the other
stuff it's a pain in the back and the
side well have you taken any medications
lately just some over-the-counter stuff
painkiller cold tablets nasal spray that
sounds okay
and some cough medicine vitamins and
acid that's a lot of medicine and some
decongestant that's too much medicine in
one day that must be why you're feeling
so bad have you been around anyone else
who's sick
my friend Donna's had a cold all week we
lifted weights last night for about an
hour
ran five miles he had to walk the last
mile it's that your usual exercise
routine yep I started it yesterday well
that explains it you exercise too much
that's all that's all a little
chiropractic treatment might help you
stay away
now about the travel documents for the
Australian group we've had everything
mailed to them right mr. Evans
we gave you the package of travel
documents to give to mr. wells the other
night at dinner before we flew home to
Sydney a white envelope about this big
yes I gave it to mr. Rashid before he
left for Lebanon Oh mr. wells needs
those documents the day after tomorrow
his group is flying in on Thursday I'll
call the courier if they can pick up a
package by 5:00 p.m. we should be okay
that gives us an hour I'll reprint the
tour information but what about the
travel guides I can't print 25 copies at
fast
I'll call copies to go and have them
reprint the travel guides they can't do
a rush job call Harper's instead they're
faster and much more reliable hello
National Express I need to get a package
to Australia ASAP if Harper's can't make
the colour copies that fast we'll take
black and white Bob are you reprinting
the tickets yep hello I need to get
twenty-five colored documents printed
right away yes it's very much a hurry
who are you calling mr. Evans what's
that
Oh my tailor your tailor
these sleeves are too long they're
driving crazy thank you everyone for
fixing my mistake with mr. wells now
I've asked Cheryl to plan a party for
his group next Friday and I'd like for
everyone to help Cheryl do you have a
plan yes I do
Marine I'd like to have you choose the
restaurant for the party
I'd love to Bob I'll let you choose the
menu you will Paul could you plan the
music yes good now Marie I called 10
restaurants and have them give us a
price for a party room these two had the
best prices the green room is a nice
restaurant great that's my favorite too
no I was thinking steak and potatoes
Hawaiian asked for fish or chicken so I
have the restaurant put together and
then you with each which do you like
better I like chicken more than fish I
guess great chicken it is now let me
guess you have a list of music choice
these look fine great I think we're all
done you see how easy it is to plan
something when we do it all together
[Music]
another wonderful dinner Cheryl thank
you you're welcome
I really enjoy cooking actually when I
was young I thought I was going to be a
chef
you could be a chef these cookies are
fantastic why didn't you become a chef
my mother talked to me out of it
she thought I would always have to work
at night she was afraid I would never
meet a man and get married she was
probably right if you were a chef you
wouldn't have met Bob how do you know
before he met you Bob only ate fast food
it's true your mother must have been
very happy when you and Bob got engaged
she was hey you'll never guess what bob
was going to be Cheryl a rock musician
that's the ballplayer no bob was going
to be a dancer he was actually in the
state ballet when he was young no
kidding
you never told me this I could have been
a great dancer what made you change your
mind the diet was too hard I had to stop
eating everything chocolate cake fried
chicken potato chips I tried that I
might have been able to do it but then
they said no more bread and butter and
butter can you believe it
and that was the end Wow Bob I never
knew do you enjoy watching ballet at all
I can't I'd like to but as soon as the
music starts I get very very hungry what
about you mr. Evans what did you think
you are going to be when you were
younger if I tell you will you try not
to laugh of course I always thought I
would have my own television program to
talk about etiquette I didn't know you
are so interested in etiquette I have
always loved etiquette I think I would
have made a great television etiquette
teacher well I think you could still do
it it's perfect for you
really why well you're very polite for
one thing you always know which fork to
use at a restaurant that's a real talent
you taught me a lot about the customs of
other cultures maybe I could still give
it a try to the conversation if your
internet yes and are leaving the table
early you have probably chosen a topic
that's taboo in their home country
find out what's acceptable what's not
coming up on international etiquette
with Evans what do you think Wow amazing
you have a real talent
I don't know I didn't know the planning
a wedding would be so hard
Marie could you give us your opinion on
a few things
I'd love to first how many people should
we invite Bob wants a small wedding 20
guests would be nice I want a large
wedding about 300 people yesterday you
said 200 I have a lot of relatives who
want to come then there's the location I
always thought I'd get married in a park
or at the beach that's so romantic
I would like to get married indoors
where I won't get wet if it's raining
that makes sense
I prefer traditional music in the
ceremony contemporary music I'd like a
long ceremony and a short reception I
want a short ceremony in a huge
celebration afterwards and I want a
chocolate cake I know how we're never
gonna agree on this
don't hurt yourself here's an idea that
might work plan a wedding that's big
enough to include all of Cheryl's family
sorry Bob in the Park on Oak Street that
has that building where you can go if it
rains you can have traditional music in
the ceremony and contemporary music at
the party and you could have two cakes
at the reception one white and one
chocolate sounds okay to me
me too
thank you so much you're amazing we
couldn't have done it without you hi
lunch time is over are you coming up to
the office I'm too tired to go back to
the office planning a wedding is hard
work
I need let's make today a holiday well
tell mr. Evans we can't come back to
work that's a great idea
what are we celebrating you're getting
married
how about national wedding day what
happens on national wedding day I don't
know why am I the one who has to think
about it why don't we make it national
singles day instead all the married
people give gifts to their single
friends buying gifts is hard work I want
to enjoy myself on our new holiday what
about a red day everybody wears red
clothes and there's dancing in the
street that goes on all night how about
national buying a friend another cup of
coffee
nice try how about national on-time day
what happens on national on-time day
remind one another to come back to work
on time
waitress so mrs. Beatty you're looking
for an exciting place for your next
vacation I usually travel to major
cities in Europe but this time I want to
go someplace different someplace away
from the city as long as it's safe
how about California the Big Sur area is
spectacular
California has lots of earthquakes
doesn't it well they have earthquakes
occasionally but not very often but it
does have earthquakes yes I'm not going
okay how about some place in Asia a
beach in Thailand co-chairing has
beautiful beaches and it's very quiet
there a quiet beach sounds nice but they
said on the news there's a monsoon in
Thailand
and what the monsoon will be over by the
time you go what else can you recommend
Australia the Australian outback is
amazing I've heard they have tornadoes
in Australia some parts where else
Jamaica Hurricanes
South Africa floods Hawaii a lot about
natural disasters don't you miss his
baby
what about Finland Finland it's wild
beautiful and very different from other
parts of Europe and nothing bad ever
happens in Finland it sounds good I'll
go to Finland great booked your tickets
[Music]
ok I just booked your tickets to
Helsinki Finland
you'll be staying at the Palace Hotel
that's great excuse me mr. Evans yes
Murray mr. Woods is on the phone he told
me to tell you it's urgent urgent he's
travelling you know yes he said there's
some kind of epidemic
what kind of epidemic it sounds like
it's that new influenza but he was
vaccinated for that before he left I
know but he told me to tell you that he
wants to fly home today on the Internet
it says only three people are sick
that is not an epidemic and it's not
like anybody's dying from this flu he
said he didn't want to be the first
where is he traveling may I ask he's in
Finland it was just booked tickets to
Finland mrs. Beatty everything will be
fine you'll get vaccinated and you'll
have nothing to worry about
I'm not going to Finland you told me
nothing bad ever happens in Finland mrs.
Beatty I can't think of anywhere in the
world you can go and be completely safe
right here in this city you could go
outside and get hit by a bus but you
can't let that stop you from doing the
things you want to do look why don't we
go to lunch and we'll talk it over
I don't think she's going anywhere
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello Bob
dining alone Paula Murray went to get
newspapers do you mind if I join you oh
please sit down
may I ask what you're reading the
history of the world the bestseller
I'm very impressed reading nonfiction
over lunch I hear that it's a very
difficult book no it's it's a pretty
easy reading I can't put it down
actually a real page-turner huh do you
think that I could borrow it when you're
done sure I usually prefer fiction
myself you know thrillers mysteries
there's nothing like curling up with a
good science fiction novel is there you
read science fiction too don't tell
anyone are you learning a lot from your
book yeah I think so so tell me what
you're reading about right now um this
part is about Great Britain really do
you mind if I take a look Cheryl hates
when I read comics that I can understand
why you can't put the book down
I think that I could borrow it then I'm
still reading this one
but I have another one I can loan I
meant this look at this the paper says
that a tornado carried a woman for 300
miles and she lived to tell about I'm
not sure if you know this but that story
isn't true it's in the paper it must be
true that paper is trash
I can't believe you're reading it what
do you mean it's fiction it's not news
nothing in there is true if you want
real news you have to read this paper
that paper is boring this one's much
more interesting woman gives birth to
cow man builds house from bread baby
with two heads come on this is offensive
storm kills 100 in Texas train accident
kills five injures more man kills wife
and son I'm sorry but all that death and
destruction is pretty offensive to me
I know that these things happened and I
know that those didn't you don't know
that you just assume that it's true
let's ask Bob and mr. Evans what paper
they read never mind let's just read
that sounds good to me
look at this
a man with four legs wacky glasses
you're wearing these are ultra high-tech
top-of-the-line state-of-the-art
cutting-edge TV glasses and you're
actually watching TV right now Yeah
right here in the corner
what are you watching the basketball
game unbelievable and Cheryl doesn't
mind this yes sorry my team
this new invention doesn't bother you
are you kidding
if I'd known how happy they would make
him I would have bought those glasses
for Bob long ago technology today is
amazing you know I wish they did invent
something that would make people who
talk on cell phones quieter this guy in
the cafe today was so loud I couldn't
hear myself talking what oh sorry I was
laughing at this guy on TV if I could
invent something it would be a thing for
Bob's car that would automatically
charge him when he goes over the speed
limit
he drives so fast sometimes but he'd
slow down if he had to pay No
is your team losing no I heard what you
said you just leave my car alone
[Music]
hi Paul wait till you see what I've got
what is it well I have this problem with
my cell phone whenever I'm traveling
with a group I can never hear a ring or
feel it vibrate so I got this thing that
lets me know whenever my phone is
ringing how does it do that it buzzes me
buzzes you know yes so I could feel it
does it work I don't know no one's told
me yet what oh hello no one's there wow
that was a big buzz it almost hurt maybe
it isn't working right it's working fine
who
strange man if ever get used to that
I'll always know whatever my phone is
ringing
Paul if I were you I would take that
thing back to the store before you hurt
yourself
I'm going I'll see you later
hope you drive okay
he'll be fine how do you know I'll stop
calling him
[Music]
did you see the politicians expect to
raise taxes again really what does the
government decide to spend our money on
now they're planning to build a stronger
military it's wrong to spend so much on
the military they should spend it on
education instead
can we please avoid discussing politics
why every time we begin talking about
politics people get mad at each other
they should spend more money on fighting
corruption if they were able to stop
corrupt officials maybe they wouldn't
need to raise our taxes that's true but
I think we need to spend more money on
the military without a strong military
the world won't be very safe that's one
way to look at it but maybe the world
would be safer and better if we try to
eliminate poverty what do you think
Cheryl I think that if I say what I
really think you'll get all mad and call
me crazy or ridiculous Cheryl don't be
so afraid we're only talking I think
that the government should spend more
money on cooking schools what most
people don't know how to cook well I
think the government should help teach
them
that's ridiculous are you crazy
use our taxes to pay for cookies look at
you you're all mad at me this is why I
never discuss politics with friends but
don't let me stop you from getting mad
at each other
are you traditional in your medical
ideas that is do you kind of believe in
Western medicine or do you like to
explore non-traditional treatments such
as acupuncture or homeopathic medicine
I don't explore non-traditional
treatments as much as I would probably
like to I think there's probably a lot
of merit in them and they haven't been
studied enough I'm more traditional than
anything else in my medication medical
practices I'm more for the naturalistic
approach I like you know more natural
herbal medicines in your opinion what
are the advantages of traditional
Western medicine and surgery
I think the enormous amount of research
and proven fact that that's behind our
medicine just makes it makes me feel
more confident what do you see is maybe
some disadvantages of Western medicine I
think at times Western medicine can make
the problem worse than trying to make
problems better
are there any non-traditional therapies
that you use I drink a lot of tea
actually so I guess that's pretty
non-traditional usually when I feel
myself coming down with something I will
take an echinacea which in herbal
medicine a prior drink a lot of orange
juice as vitamin C helps you but if I
feel really sick then I'll take a cough
medicine could you tell me what your
career or occupation is I'm an
elementary school teacher my career path
will be in marketing helping companies
build their brand and help market
products to it the general consumer I
work in television and I would like to
eventually produce and direct did you
think that you'd be in marketing when
you were a child no I thought I'd be
President of the United States or drive
a fire truck what made teaching a good
career for you first of all I love
children and I liked the idea of
imparting some of my knowledge to young
ones
everybody has skills talents and
abilities so you know some people are
artistic others have mechanical ability
what would you say are some of your
skills I'd say I have a little artistic
ability I did a lot of art in school I
could question my skills and talents
would be coming up with new ideas
different ideas creative ideas that kind
of build a buzz around a product do you
think that talents and abilities of
genetic I think they're a combination of
both genetics and environment I think
that you are born with certain
qualities that your parents I think or
having and just living with the people
around you and and and learning from
your teachers and those that you're
constantly interacting with you pick up
certain skills you're from Germany what
is a wedding like in Germany well first
of all you have to have a civil ceremony
where you go to to the city hall and
well you make it really you make
everything official and then
traditionally you go to church and have
their religious ceremony and is there a
wedding reception afterward usually
there is of course after church when is
everybody's waiting for the groom and
the bride coming out and throwing rice
at them and flowers and then the whole
crews going to a nice place and having
dinner and having a party you mentioned
that your family is originally from
Ghana could you tell me a little bit
about the courtship and marriage
ceremonies of your country there is a
traditional sometimes they do involve
like the American type of wedding - very
traditional you walk down the aisle and
they also in there is also the
traditional part in African culture
where the clothing the outfits it's much
longer sometimes it can go into the next
day some people it extends tell me about
the reception they find a place to go to
or it's a outside sometimes it's a big
tent like it just depends on the bride
and groom and what they want and there's
tons dancing traditional dancing eating
lots of food sometimes you have somebody
come in and talk about how they know him
and how how good he is and what he's
done and you know people giving thoughts
of wisdom of how to be together and it
just it's just really a great thing how
do you feel about prohibiting smoking
indoors as a smoker I don't appreciate
it all the time but I can I can
understand why I think it's fantastic I
think it's great if you don't if you go
to restaurants and nobody can smoke the
food tastes better and your clothes
don't smell how about censorship of
books or movies by a government I am
100% against censorship of any books or
movies or any expression of creativity
and I feel that when government's tried
to censor books or movies then it
creates a sort of atmosphere of fear and
people don't get to don't have already
access to information that should be
available to them if you could tell me
maybe two things that you think are big
problems in the world today I think one
of the biggest problems is war and I
think another big problem is racism in
this world
and of those could you tell me you know
a little bit more about what you think
could be done to alleviate these
problems I think issue with both
problems it's mostly about understanding
each other and sitting down on a table
and talk and get to know each other and
and be able to make more compromises and
understand different cultures and
reasons why people do certain things
certain ways and I think we would all be
much happier communication communication
that's the that's the clue exactly yeah